[
  {
    "question": "false || true",
    "answers": ["false", "true", "undefined"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null && false",
    "answers": ["null", "false", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "(false && 'bar') || 'foo'",
    "answers": ["false", "'bar'", "'foo'"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' || 'bar'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "'bar'", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' && 'bar' || 'quz'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "'bar'", "'quz'"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!'foo' && 'bar'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "'bar'", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' && !(false && null)",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "false", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!undefined || 'foo'",
    "answers": ["true", "'foo'", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' || !!'bar'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "(null && 'foo') || 'bar'",
    "answers": ["null", "'foo'", "'bar'"]
  },

  {
    "question": "(null || []).push('foo')",
    "answers": ["null", "['foo']", "1"]
  },

  {
    "question": "('foo' || 'bar').indexOf('f')",
    "answers": ["-1", "0", "1"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null || 'foo' && 'bar'",
    "answers": ["null", "'foo'", "'bar'"]
  },

  {
    "question": "[] && [].push('foo')",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "['foo']", "1"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null || [] || {}",
    "answers": ["null", "[]", "'{}'"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!!!'foo'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "![].length",
    "answers": ["false", "true", "0"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' && ('bar' || null)",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "'bar'", "null"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' !== ('foo' && 'bar')",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "2 > (3 && 0)",
    "answers": ["false", "true", "2"]
  },

  {
    "question": "false && false",
    "answers": ["false", "true", "null"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!false || 'foo'",
    "answers": ["false", "'foo'", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "1 >= 1",
    "answers": ["1", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!!['foo'].indexOf('foo')",
    "answers": ["0", "1", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "0 == false",
    "answers": ["0", "false", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "1 > 2",
    "answers": ["1", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "!!'foo'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "'foo' == 'bar'",
    "answers": ["'foo'", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "0 || 1",
    "answers": ["0", "1", "true"]
  },

  {
    "question": "1 === true",
    "answers": ["1", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null == undefined",
    "answers": ["null", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null == 0",
    "answers": ["null", "0", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null > -1",
    "answers": ["null", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "null < 1",
    "answers": ["null", "true", "false"]
  },

  {
    "question": "false == ''",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "''"]
  },

  {
    "question": "(function(){}).length == 0",
    "answers": ["0", "false", "true"]
  }
]
